Micael Silva



micaelsilva.work@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mykaa



+351 968139550



https://mmykaa.github.io/

Summary

I started my journey in game programming when I was 14 to occupy my free time. Nowadays I am a Gameplay Programmer with strong skills in C# and C++, an expert user of Unity & Unreal Engine and have developed both personal and team projects within the engines.

Experience



📗 Network / Gameplay Programmer @ Zapowa Games

Zapowa Games

Nov 2021 - Present (10 months +) Gameplay / Networking / UI Programming Unreal Engine / C++

📘 Tools / Gameplay Programmer @ WestFell Studios

WestFell Studios Feb 2021 - Sep 2021 (8 months) Gameplay / Tools / UI Programming Unity / C#

Education



Polytechnic of Leiria

Undergraduate, Games and Multimedia Oct 2020 - Aug 2023

Licenses & Certifications



G Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design - Google

GRRV23TQ2BYA

Skills

Unreal Engine • C++ • Unity • C# • User Experience (UX)